A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, New York Office, Series 22 FA365
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appointments Office, 1959-1965; 1; 9 Cubic Feet
  - Boston, Massachusetts, June 28, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    1. Republican Key Club Dinner 2. State Republican Rally, Boston Garden
  - Saratoga Springs, New York; Schoharie, New York, June 30, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 265)
    Saratoga Springs 1. Tour of State Park, dedication of new pool 2. Luncheon at Hall of Springs Schoharie 1. Schoharie Valley 250th Anniversary
  - Regrets, June 1962 (Box 7, Folder 266)
    1. Finger Lakes State Parks Commission 2. Governor David L. Lawrence (Pennsylvania) 3. Westchester Professional Auto Driving Schools 4. Mr. Peter W. Tacon (wanted to see NAR) 5. Spanish Catholic Action 6. All Republican Conference 7. Republican Organization of the Rockaways 8. Colonie Young Republican Club 9. American Society of Travel Agents 10. Letchworth State Park 11. Women's Republican Club of Beacon 12. Nursing Home Association 13. Testimonial Dinner for Judge Angelo Graci 14. Rose Festival of Newark, New York 15. Fulton, New York Civic Celebration 16. Strawberry Dance on the Allegheny Reservation
  - Chautauqua, New York, July 4, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    1. Independence Day Program
  - New York, New York, July 5, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 268)
    1. New York City Council of Bishops of the African Methodist Episcopal Church
  - Washington, DC, July 6, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    1. Candidates Conference Dinner
  - New York, New York, July 9, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Averill Park, New York, July 16, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    1. Rensselaer County Republican Committee
  - Nassau-Suffolk Counties, New York, July 17-19, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    July 17 1. Stony Brook - Briefing by local leaders 2. Tour of State University at Stony Brook 3. Flower Field - Visit Gyrodene Plant 4. West Brentwood - Luncheon with local medical leaders 5. Plainview - Engineer's Hill Industrial Park 6. Plainview - Dedication of Aerojet-Delft Co. 7. Jones Beach - Governor's Day 8. Jones Beach - Dinner with local leaders 9. East Meadow - Concert, Nassau County Park July 18 1. Garden City - Breakfast with labor leaders 2. East Meadow - Meeting with the Nassau County Committee on the Development of Mitchell Field 3. Garden City - Meeting with the Board of Trustees, Nassau Community College 4. Helicopter Tour of South Shore Parkland 5. East Meadow - Luncheon with Long Island Home Builders Institute 6. Sag Harbor - Tour of Whaling Museum 7. Shelter Island - Suffolk County Republican Committee 8. Aquebogue - Visit to Long Island Duck farm 9. Riverhead - Dinner with local business leaders July 19 1. Riverhead - Breakfast with agricultural leaders 2. Baiting Hollow - Visit to potato farm 3. Baiting Hollow - Visit to Boy Scout Camp 4. Upton - Brookhaven National Laboratory 5. Long Island Rail Road traveling luncheon 6. Albertson - Visit to Abilities, Inc. 7. East Hempstead - Visit to home for the aged 8. Press conference 9. Roosevelt Field - Dinner with press, radio, television executives 10. Massapequa - Town meeting
  - New York, New York, July 20, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 273)
    1. Jackie Robinson Dinner
  - Regrets, July 1962 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    1. Dr. James A. Rogers 2. "Starboard Watch" - Mr. Paul L. Norton 3. Republican Club of New Rochelle 4. New York State Association of Chiefs of Police 5. Mrs. Cecile F. Minturn 6. Sesquicentennial of Kendall, New York 7. Sesquicentennial of Perinton, New York 8. Belleayre Mountain Ski Center 9. United States Army Reserve Center, Penn Yan, New York
  - Jamaica, New York (Regret), August 3-8, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    1. Jamaica Independence Celebration
  - Massena, New York, August 3, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    1. Federation of Women's Republican Clubs
  - Saratoga Springs, New York, August 4, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 277)
    1. Presentation of Whitney Stakes Trophy
  - Schroon Lake, New York; Glens Falls, New York, August 7, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 278)
    Schroon Lake 1. New York State Sheriffs Association Glens Falls, New York 1. Filming at Finch and Prawn Paper Mill
  - Schenectady, New York; Middletown, New York; Norwich, New York, August 8, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 279)
    Schenectady 1. Filming at Union College Middletown 1. Orange County Fair a. Luncheon b. Tour c. Filming Norwich 1. Chenango County Fair a. Buffet b. Parade c. Speech
  - Oswego County, New York, August 9, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 280)
    1. Chamber of Commerce luncheon 2. Tour of Sandy Creek Fair 3. Fort Ontario visit 4. Oswego County Republican Committee
  - South Shore of Long Island, New York, August 19, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 281)
    1. Tour of beaches by helicopter a. Coney Island, walk boardwalk b. Rockaway Beach, walk boardwalk c. Jones Beach, walk boardwalk
  - Albany, New York, August 21, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 282)
    1. Senate and Assembly Candidates meeting
  - Poughkeepsie, New York, August 22, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 283)
    1. Businessman's luncheon 2. Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) for Senior Citizens 3. Rhinebeck - Dutchess County Fair 4. Dutchess County Republican Committee Picnic
  - Franklin County, New York, August 23, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 284)
    1. Malone - Elks Club luncheon 2. Franklin County Fair
  - Jefferson and Lewis Counties, New York, August 24, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 285)
    1. Lowville - Rally and luncheon 2. Watertown - Opening of Republican Headquarters 3. Jefferson County Fair 4. Jefferson and Lewis Counties Fund Raising Dinner 5. Live TV appearance
  - Buffalo, New York; Ontario, Canada; Hamburg, New York, August 26, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 286)
    Buffalo 1. Executive Motel - Private luncheon 2. Buffalo Canoe Club "Lightning" Regatta Ontario, Canada 1. Erie County Republican Committee Picnic Hamburg 1. Erie County Fair a. Tour b. Dinner with County Fair Board
  - Brooklyn, New York, August 28, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 287)
    1. Filming of NAR appearance at Negro Church
  - New York, New York; Syracuse, New York, August 29, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 288)
    New York City 1. Dedication of lower level of George Washington Bridge 2. Reception and lunch, Ross Dock Arena Syracuse 1. Onondaga County Republican Dinner 2. Annual State Farm Dinner
  - Onondaga and Wayne Counties, New York, August 30, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 289)
    1. New York State Fair a. Breakfast b. Tour c. Governor's luncheon d. Meeting with Milk Committee e. Cattle judging f. Press conference 2. Newark, New York - Press conference 3. Wayne County Republican Committee Picnic
  - Regrets, August 1962 (Box 8, Folder 290)
    1. 138th Airborne Group 2. Lincoln Republican Club Clambake 3. Southern Herkimer County Republican Club 4. Division of Employment Office, Watertown 5. Meeting with United Nations Representatives 6. Warren County Republican Committee 7. New York State Women's Relief Corps Home 8. Red Hook, New York 150th Anniversary 9. Middleburgh, New York 250th Anniversary 10. Clarence E. Kilburn (offering accommodations) 11. Erie County Fair 12. Central Canada Exhibition 13. Palmer College of Chiropractic 14. Puerto Rican Absentee Voters Association
  - Regrets, September 3, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 291)
    1. Columbia County Fair a. Tour b. Grandstand program d. Tour cattle and 4-H buildings 2. Chatham - Reception with Alexander Aldrich
  - Albany, New York, September 4, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 292)
    1. Luncheon with leading physicians
  - Albany, New York; Kiamesha Lake, New York, September 5, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 293)
    Albany 1. New York State Police Academy Graduation Kiamesha Lake 1. Sullivan County Republican Committee Dinner
  - Monroe County, New York (postponed due to New York State Primary), September 6, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 294)
    1. Monroe County Republican Committee
  - New York, New York (postponed), September 7, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 295)
    1. Emancipation Proclamation Dinner
  - Suffolk County, New York, September 8, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 296)
    1. Patchogue - Suffolk County Republican outing
  - Seneca and Cayuga Counties, New York, September 9, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 297)
    1. Seneca County Republican Committee Picnic 2. Cayuga County Republican Committee Picnic
  - New York, New York, September 10, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 298)
    1. New York State American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Convention
  - Albany, New York; Schenectady, New York; Kiamesha Lake, New York, September 11, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 299)
    Albany 1. Legislative Candidates Meeting Schenectady 1. Consolidated Diesel Electric Corporation Kiamesha Lake 1. County Officers Association Banquet
  - New York, New York, September 12, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 300)
    1. "Citizens for Rockefeller-Javits," Headquarters Opening 2. Brotherhood in Action building site ceremony 3. Emancipation Proclamation Dinner
  - Garden City, New York, September 13, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 301)
    1. National Association of Labor Relations Agencies 2. Nassau County Republican Recruits Dinner
  - Buffalo, New York, September 16-20, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 302)
    1. New York Republican State Convention
  - Albany, New York; Saranac Lake, New York; Elizabethtown, New York; Lake Placid, New York, September 21, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 303)
    Albany 1. "Rural Citizens Committee for Rockefeller" Saranac Lake 1. Rally at Saranac Lake Armory Elizabethtown 1. Rally at Essex County Court House Lake Placid 1. Associated Industries of New York State
  - Washington, DC; Staten Island, New York; New York, New York, September 22, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 304)
    Washington, D.C. 1. Anniversary of the Signing of the Emancipation Proclamation Staten Island 1. Richmond County Republican Committee Picnic New York City 1. San Gennaro Festival rally
  - New York, New York, September 23, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 305)
    1. Opening of Philharmonic Hall, Lincoln Center
  - New York, New York, September 24, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 306)
    1. New York District of Kiwanis International 2. "Victory Vanguard," TV Campaign "Kick-off"
  - New York, New York, September 25, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 307)
    1. The Touchdown Club of New York "Kick-off" 2. Opening of New York Republican State Committee Campaign Headquarters
  - Montreal, Canada; Clinton County, New York, September 26, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 308)
    Montreal 1. New York State Department of Commerce Office a. Opening b. Press conference c. Reception and luncheon 2. Montreal City Hall Clinton County 1. Champlain - Atlas Missile Site #1 2. Champlain - Rally 3. Rouses Point - Rally 4. Chazy - William H. Miner Agricultural Research Institute 5. Plattsburgh - Rally
  - St. Lawrence and Madison Counties, New York, September 27, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 309)
    1. Massena - Opening, St. Lawrence County Republican Headquarters 2. Potsdam - Rallies (2) 3. Royal Pearce Farm 4. Canton - Rally 5. Ogdensburg - Luncheon, Women's Republican Club 6. Ogdensburg - Tour Downtown Shopping Area 7. Oneida - Rally 8. Hamilton - Madison County Republican Committee 9. Colgate University Student Meeting
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, September 28, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 310)
    1. Herkimer County - Remington Arms Plant 2. Herkimer County - Tour of Ilion 3. Herkimer County - Tour of Little Falls 4. Fulton County - Johnstown, new office building 5. Fulton County - Johnstown, luncheon 6. Hamilton County - Wells, rally 7. Fulton County - Gloversville, rally 8. Montgomery County - Amsterdam, appearance 9. Montgomery County - Tour of Amsterdam 10. Montgomery County - Amsterdam, rally
  - New York, New York, September 29, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 311)
    1. Fifth Annual Steuben Parade
  - Regrets, September 1962 (Box 9, Folder 312)
    1. District 65 of American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) 2. Niagara County Republican Committee 3. Pittsburgh Freedom Rally 4. Utica Migrant Labor Child Care Center 5. United Steel Workers 6. Eastern States Exposition 7. Colonie Young Republican Club 8. Beacon Women's Republican Clubs 9. St. Matthew's Evangelical Lutheran Church 10. Northwest Airlines (offer to fly NAR) 11. Department of Mental Hygiene 12. Willard State Hospital 13. 4th Assembly District, Manhattan 14. New York State Association of Tobacco Distributors 15. Junior Chamber of Commerce of the Bronx 16. Dinner with Martin Luther King 17. Women's Republican Club of Saratoga County 18. Ohio Municipal League 19. Montgomery County Women's Republican Club 20. Alcoa Products, Inc.
  - Westchester County, New York, October 1, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 313)
    1. White Plains - Women's Rally 2. Chappaqua - Tour, "Readers Digest" Plant 3. Pleasantville - Tour, General Precision Laboratories 4. Pleasantville - Tour, Pleasantville Instrument Corporation 5. Mount Vernon - Tour, Reuben H. Donnelly Corporation 6. North Tarrytown - Tour, Chevrolet Plant 7. Westchester Republican Town and City Chairmen and Candidates Dinner 8. White Plains - Rally
  - Ithaca, New York; New York, New York, October 2, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 314)
    Ithaca 1. Tour, National Cash Register Company 2. Rally, Tompkins County Republican Headquarters 3. Cornell University Dedication of new quadrangle New York City 1. Museum of Modern Art Dinner and Reception
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 3, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 315)
    1. Putnam County - Carmel, rally 2. Dutchess County - Poughkeepsie, tour, rally 3. Columbia County - Hudson, rally 4. Greene County - Catskill, rally 5. Ulster County - Kingston, motor tour, rally 6. Ulster County - Accord, dinner
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 4, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 316)
    1. Delaware County - Sidney, tour of plant 2. Otsego County - Oneonta, tour, luncheon 3. Schoharie County - Cobleskill, rally 4. Albany County - Albany, Latham, Cohoes, rallies
  - New York, New York, October 6, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 317)
    1. "Salute of Women" luncheon, reception 2. New York State Convention of the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) 3. Testimonial Dinner for Lawrence E. Gerosa
  - New York, New York, October 7, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 318)
    1. Pulaski Day Parade
  - New York, New York, October 9, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 319)
    1. Ground breaking, New York State Pavilion, 1964 World's Fair 2. Walking tour Fulton Street, Brooklyn 3. Kings County republican Headquarters Opening 4. "Pulse of New York" luncheon 5. Citizens for Rockefeller and Javits Finance Committee Reception 6. Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation Dinner
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 10, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 320)
    1. Niagara County - Exchange Club Luncheon 2. Niagara County - Lockport, plant tour 3. Orleans County - Medina, rally 4. Orleans County - Albion, rally 5. Genesee County - Batavia, rally, dinner
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 11, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 321)
    1. Buffalo - civil Service Employers Association 2. Dedication of South Grand Island Bridge 3. Ground breaking of North Grand Island Bridge 4. Niagara County - Robert Moses Power Plant 5. Tour Lewiston-Queenstown International Bridge and Canadian Toll Plaza 6. Niagara Falls County Club, luncheon 7. Tour Bell Aerosystems Company 8. New York City - General Membership Meeting, Local Union No. 3, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) 9. New York City - Annual Columbus Day Dinner
  - New York, New York; Lake Placid, New York, October 12, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 322)
    New York City (AM) 1. Walking Tour of Herald Square 2. Columbus Day Parade (reviewing stand) Lake Placid 1. New York State Conservation Council New York City (PM) 1. La Hispaniad-Spanish Institute, Inc.
  - New York, New York, October 13, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 323)
    1. Hudson Division American Radio Delay League 2. Ukrainian Congress Committee of America
  - New York, New York, October 14, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 324)
    1. Federation of Jewish Philanthropies
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 15, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 325)
    1. Rockland County - Nanuet, rally 2. Orange County - Newburgh, motor tour 3. Orange County - Newburgh, tour of plant 4. Orange County - Newburgh, luncheon 5. Albany County - Albany, New York State Associated Press Association Annual Meeting
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 16, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 326)
    1. Chemung County - Tour Westinghouse Plant 2. Chemung County - Elmira College, luncheon 3. Tioga County - Waverly, rally 4. Tioga County - Owego, rally 5. Broome County - Endicott, appearance 6. Broome County - Vestal, rally 7. Broome County - Johnson City, rally
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 17, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 327)
    1. Broome County - Dedication Harpur College 2. Cayuga County - Auburn, tour plant, rally 3. New York City - Protestant Council of the City of New York Annual Testimonial Dinner
  - New York, New York, October 18, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 328)
    1. Walking Tour 42nd Street Area 2. Garment Center Rally 3. Lunch with local residents 4. Walking Tour Washington Square Park Area 5. Ground breaking, Boys Brotherhood Republic 6. Walking Tour Lenox Avenue, 116th Street 7. Walking Tour Lexington Avenue 8. All-American Committee of the New York State Republican Campaign Committee 9. Rally, Cooper Union 10. Square Deal Republican Club
  - New York, New York, October 19, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 329)
    1. Staff Work Day
  - Nassau County, New York, October 20, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 330)
    1. Whistle Stop Trip on Long Island Rail Road (LIRR) - Seaford, Wantaugh, Bellmore, Merrick, Freeport 2. Freeport - Family Service Association Youth Project 3. Freeport - 75th Anniversary Parade 4. Rockville Centre - Republican Headquarters 5. Franklin Square - Luncheon 6. Levittown - Rally, appearances 7. Tour Long Island Fair, Roosevelt Raceway 8. Old Brookville - Reception, dinner 9. Garden City - Forget-Me-Not Ball
  - New York, New York, October 21, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 331)
    1. WCBS-TV taping 2. Antioch Baptist Church
  - Rochester, New York, October 22, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 332)
    1. Reception, rally
  - Erie County, New York, October 23, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 333)
    1. Williamsville - Veteran's Tribute to Congressman William E. Miller 2. Buffalo - WKBW-TV Special Program
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 24, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 334)
    1. Chautauqua County - Dunkirk, rally 2. Chautauqua County - Jamestown, luncheon 3. Steuben County - Corning, reception 4. Cattaraugus County - Olean, rally 5. Allegheny County - Wellsville, parade and rally 6. Allegheny County - Wellsville, dinner
  - New York, New York; Schenectady, New York, October 25, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 335)
    New York City 1. WOR Radio 2. WCBS-TV Schenectady 1. WRGB-TV
  - Kings County, New York, October 26, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 336)
    1. Motor tour of Flatbush Avenue 2. Walking tour of Flatbush Avenue 3. Lunch, Dubrow's Cafeteria 4. Walking tour of Kings Highway 5. Walking tour of Fifth Avenue and 51st Street 6. Walking tour of 86th Street and Fifth Avenue 7. Motor tour of Bedford-Stuyvesant Area 8. Kings County Republican Committee rally
  - Westchester County, New York, October 27, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 337)
    1. WLIB Studio taping 2. Rye - Rally 3. White Plains - Luncheon 4. Elmsford - Rally 5. Yonkers - Luncheon, rally 6. Pelham - Rally 7. New Rochelle - Rally 8. Mamaroneck - Rally 9. Scarsdale - Reception, dinner 10. Mount Pleasant - Dinner dance
  - New York, New York, October 28, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 338)
    1. Spanish fiesta 2, "Today" Show appearance 3. Annual Grand Council Columbia Associations
  - New York, New York; Oneida and Onondaga Counties, New York, October 29, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 339)
    New York City 1. Annual Conference of the National Narcotic Enforcement Officers Association Oneida and Onondaga Counties 1. Utica - Luncheon 2. Verona - Rural meeting 3. Meeting with General Dwight D. Eisenhower 4. Syracuse - Onondaga 1962 Republican Dinner
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, October 30, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 340)
    1. Warren County - Airport, rally 2. Rensselaer County - Troy, rally and dinner 3. Schenectady County - Schenectady, rally
  - Queens County, New York, October 31, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 341)
    1. Jamaica-Queens Candidates Luncheon 2. Walking Tour, Jamaica Shopping Area 3. Walking Tour, Main Street and Roosevelt Avenue 4. Walking Tour, Fresh Meadow Shopping Area 5. Walking Tour, Hillside Avenue Bus Area 6. Queens Village - Dinner 7. Astoria - Motor Tour, rally 8. Elmhurst - Appearance
  - Regrets, October 1962 (Box 11, Folder 342)
    1. National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Voter Registration Drive in Harlem 2. Broome County Fair 3. Garsite Products Plant 4. New York Automobile Dealers 5. League of Women Voters of Albany County 6. Graduate School of Journalism of Columbia University 7. Ossining Young Republican Club 8. Scarsdale Women's Club 9. Editors of "Evening Press" and "Sun Bulletin" 10. Mineola Fair 11. Empire State Petroleum Association 12. Rosary Hill College 13. Harrison Republican Club 14. Lakeland Republican Club 15. Opening of Boulevard Mall (Buffalo) 16. "Action Course in Practical Politics" 17. Grand Council Columbia Associations 18. New York University, University Heights Center 19. New York State Home Builders Association 20. National Communications Symposium 21. American Society of Newspaper Editors 22. National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials (NAHRO)
  - New York, New York; Nassau and Suffolk Counties, New York, November 1, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 343)
    New York City 1. New York City Teachers Committee Reception 2. New York State Labor Committee Nassau-Suffolk Counties 1. Commack - Nassau-Suffolk rally
  - Bronx County, New York, November 2, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 344)
    1. Bronx County Republican Headquarters 2. Walking Tour, Hearns Department Store 3. Walking Tour, Alexander's Department Store 4. Lunch, Chateau Pelham 5. Walking Tour, Macy's 6. Walking Tour, 161st Street and Prospect Avenue 7. Rally, Evander Childs High School
  - New York State Campaign Appearances, November 3, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 345)
    1. Queens County - Flushing, rally 2. Suffolk County - Heckscher Parkway Opening 3. Suffolk County - Brentwood, outdoor greeting 4. Suffolk County - East Northport, luncheon 5. Suffolk County - North Babylon, rally 6. Suffolk County - West Babylon, rally 7. Suffolk County - Melville, rally 8. New York City - Mass rally
  - New York, New York, November 4, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 346)
    1. WNBC-TV Program "Direct Line"
  - New York, New York, November 5, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 347)
    1. WCBS-TV taping - "All Republican Candidates" 2. Brooklyn - Public appearance, Borough Hall 3. Public Appearance, Union Square 4. Public Appearance, 96th Street and Broadway 5. Walking Tour, 125th Street
  - Election Day 1962, November 6, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 348)
  - New Hampshire, November 8, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 349)
    1. Dartmouth College, dedication of new center
  - New York, New York, November 25, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 350)
    1. Museum of Modern Art, ground breaking for new building, reception
  - Regrets, November 1962 (Box 11, Folder 351)
    1. Bronx Board of Education Day Classes 2. Governor's Conference on Youth 3. Eighth Annual Congress of the Diocesan Council of Catholic Youth (Worcester, Massachusetts)
  - New York, New York, December 4, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 352)
    1. Tax Foundation
  - New York, New York, December 5, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 353)
    1. National Association of Manufacturers
  - New York, New York, December 6, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 354)
    1. Dinner in honor of General Eisenhower
  - New York, New York, December 7, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 355)
  - New York, New York, December 13, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 356)
    1. Urban League of Greater New York
  - Regrets, December 1962 (Box 11, Folder 357)